Yamisa Majija

• A755b Orange Street, Site C, Khayelitsha, 7784 • majijayamisa@gmail.com • 0814309896

Intro

Responsible and reliable with good time management and customer service skills. Also, possess proven communication skills and a strong work ethic. I believe my fast learning abilities, skills, experience and relevant studies make me the perfect fit for this position.

Education

Matric National Senior Certificate - Centre Of Science And

2017 **Technology**

Systems Capaciti learnership - College of Cape Town
Development I had the opportunity to learn Systems Development.

Jan 2018- Jun 2018

(NQF 5)

Skills

- Good analytical and planning skills.
- Good Accuracy and attention to details.
- · Excellent team player.
- Hard worker and a fast learner.
- Good communication skills

Work Experience

Younglings SA Web Developer (intern) - Woodstock

July 2018- Jan 2019 Used different programming languages such as Java,

JavaScript, C# and also HTML and CSS.

Gelato Mania Sales/Cleaner - V&A Waterfront

Sept 2019- Jan 2020 Responsibilities include sales, cleaning the shop and

waitressing.

Capital Ship

Security Controller - Bellville

Mar 2020- Jan 2021 Responsible for reporting emergencies I get from security

guards to EMC, SAPS, Fire Station etc.

Also basic admin work such as logging guards, sending emails,

book records etc.

References

Younglings SA Mr Carelse - 0817275928

Gelato Mania Shift Leader- 0726279899

Capital Ship Khathala Zahra- 0742889704 Security